{
    "response_code": 0,
    "trivia": [
        {
            "question": "Which actor is the only one who's appeared in every single Skywalker Saga movie to date?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Anthony Daniels",
            "alias": ["Anthony D", "A Daniels"],
            "category": "sw",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which stormtrooper wasn't able to complete his mission in Star Wars: The Force Awakens?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "FN-2187",
            "alias": ["Finn", "Fin", "FN2187", "FN 2187"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of vehicle did Rey live in?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "AT-AT",
            "alias": ["atat", "at at", "AT-AT Walker"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to Master Yoda, how many Sith are always out there?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "2",
            "alias": ["Two"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "What limb did Anakin lose in his fight with Count Dooku?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Right Arm",
            "alias": ["His right arm"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who played the part of Commander Cody?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Temuera Morrison",
            "alias": ["T Morrison"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who killed Jabba?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Leia",
            "alias": ["Princess Leia", "Leia Organa"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did the Clone Wars begin?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Geonosis",
            "alias": ["Geonosis arena"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the color of C-3PO's arm in Star Wars: The Force Awakens?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Red",
            "alias": ["Red"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who adopted Padmé Amidala's daughter?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["B Organa", "Bail"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "10"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who first and most famously played the part of Chewbacca?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Peter Mayhew",
            "alias": ["P Mayhew"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "11"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the job that Finn told Han Solo he had on Starkiller base?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sanitation",
            "alias": ["Sanitation worker", "in sanitation"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "12"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where were the Hoth sequences filmed? (Real world country)", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Norway",
            "alias": ["Norway"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "13"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old was Anakin Skywalker during the battle on Geonosis?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "20",
            "alias": ["Twenty"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who fixed the hyperdrive on the Millennium Falcon?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "R2-D2",
            "alias": ["R2D2", "R2 D2", "R2", "Rtoo", "Artoo"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "15"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who killed Jango Fett?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mace Windu",
            "alias": ["Mace", "Windu"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "16"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which bounty hunter was trying to capture Han Solo when Greedo arrived first?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Danz Borin",
            "alias": ["Danz", "Borin"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who taught Lando Calrissian how to pilot a ship?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Han Solo",
            "alias": ["Han", "Solo"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "18"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many lightsabers does General Grievous wield in his fight with Obi-Wan on Utapau?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "4",
            "alias": ["Four"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "19"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who offered to lead the attack against the Death Star?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Lando",
            "alias": ["Lando Calrissian"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "20"
        },
        {
            "question": "What species is Chewbacca?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Wookiee",
            "alias": ["Wookkiee", "Wookie", "Wookkie"],
            "category": "sw",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of the standard rifle carried by the clone troopers?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "DC-15A",
            "alias": ["dc15a", "dc15-a", "dc-15-a", "dc-15 a"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "22"
        },
        {
            "question": "Count Dooku was one of how many Jedi who had left the Jedi Order?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "20",
            "alias": ["Twenty"],
            "category": "sw",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "23"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who joined Poe Dameron in his X-Wing in order to help destroy Starkiller?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "BB-8",
            "alias": ["BB8", "BB 8"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "24"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who gave FN-2187 his new name when they found out that he didn't have a real name?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Poe",
            "alias": ["Poe Dameron", "Dameron"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "25"
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of weapon did Han Solo carry?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "DL-44 pistol",
            "alias": ["DL-44", "DL44", "DL44 pistol", "DL-44 blaster", "DL44 blaster", "DL 44"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "26"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who provided the voice for General Grievous?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Matthew Wood",
            "alias": ["M Wood"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "27"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many Rathtars did Han Solo and Chewbacca have on their ship?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "3",
            "alias": ["Three"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "28"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Grand Moff Tarkin's impression of Leia's presence on board the Death Star?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Charming",
            "alias": ["Charming to the last"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "29"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many meals does Jabba consume per day?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "9",
            "alias": ["Nine"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "30"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Yoda tell Obi-Wan after he had said 'That boy is our last hope'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "No, there is another",
            "alias": ["No there is another", "No. There is another", "No. There is another.", "No, there is another.", "No there is another."],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "31"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who provided the voice of Darth Vader?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "James Earl Jones",
            "alias": ["James E Jones", "J Earl Jones"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "32"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'So this is how liberty dies... with thunderous applause'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Padmé Amidala",
            "alias": ["Padme", "Padme Amidala", "Senator Amidala", "Padmé"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "33"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the language of the Wookiees?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Shyriiwook",
            "alias": ["Shyriiwook"],
            "category": "sw",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "34"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who freed Han Solo from carbonite?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Leia",
            "alias": ["Princess Leia", "Leia Organa"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "35"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Feel. Don't think. Trust your instincts?'", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn",
            "alias": ["Qui-Gon", "Qui Gon Jinn", "Qui Gon", "QuiGon", "Qui-Gon Jin"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "36"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old was Padmé when she was elected the Queen of Naboo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "14",
            "alias": ["Fourteen"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "37"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whose lightsaber did Luke Skywalker receive from Obi-Wan?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Anakin's",
            "alias": ["Anakins", "Anakin"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "38"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who told Rey, 'I am no Jedi, but I know the Force'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Maz Kanata",
            "alias": ["Maz", "Kanata"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "39"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Anakin say Padmé resembled when she questioned the state of the Republic?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "A Separatist",
            "alias": ["Separatist"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "40"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to Obi-Wan, what is a lightsaber to a Jedi?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Their life",
            "alias": ["life", "there life", "your life"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "41"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Kylo Ren's given name?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ben",
            "alias": ["Ben Solo"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "42"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who directed Return of the Jedi?",
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Richard Marquand",
            "alias": ["Marquand"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "43"
        },
        {
            "question": "What species is Jabba?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Hutt",
            "alias": ["Huttese"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "44"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Han Solo call the Kanjiklub?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Little freaks",
            "alias": ["freaks", "a bunch of little freaks", "bunch of little freaks"],
            "category": "tfa",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "45"
        },
        {
            "question": "On what planet did Han Solo meet Chewbacca?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mimban",
            "alias": ["Mimban."],
            "category": "solo",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "46"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the cell number where Princess Leia was imprisoned?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "2187",
            "alias": ["21-87"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "47"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Jabba's complete name?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jabba Desilijic Tiure",
            "alias": ["Jabba Desilijictiure"],
            "category": "rotj",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "48"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many spires does the Jedi Temple have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "5",
            "alias": ["Five"],
            "category": "sw",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "49"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the birth planet of Han Solo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Corellia",
            "alias": ["Corellia."],
            "category": "solo",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "50"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wo was Cloud City's computer liaison officer?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Lobot",
            "alias": ["Lo"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "51"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Luke, don't give in to hate'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obi", "Obiwan", "Obi-wan", "Kenobi"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "52"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Vader need to contact when he asked Admiral Piett to move the Executor so they could send a clear signal?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Emperor Palpatine",
            "alias": ["Palpatine", "palps", "The Emperor"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "53"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Luke's tail gunner in the Battle of Hoth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Dak Ralter",
            "alias": ["Dak"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "54"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'You have a responsibility to me, so don't do anything foolish'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "C-3PO",
            "alias": ["C3PO", "C 3PO", "C3P0", "3PO"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "55"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did General Rieekan order to have the power in Echo Base rerouted to?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The energy shield",
            "alias": ["energy shield"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "56"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'He's no good to me dead'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Boba Fett",
            "alias": ["Boba"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "57"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which actor played Wedge Antilles?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Denis Lawson",
            "alias": ["Denis L", "Lawson"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "58"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many locations was the tractor beam coupled to the main reactor on the Death Star?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Seven",
            "alias": ["7"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "59"
        },
        {
            "question": "What mission did Princess Leia give Obi-Wan Kenobi?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "To take R2-D2 to Alderaan",
            "alias": ["take R2-D2 to Alderaan", "take R2D2 to Alderaan", "To take R2D2 to Alderaan"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "60"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character did Shelagh Fraser play?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Beru Lars",
            "alias": ["Beru", "Berru"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "61"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'into the garbage chute, fly boy!'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Princess Leia",
            "alias": ["Leia", "Leia Organa"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "62"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character did Phil Brown play?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Owen Lars",
            "alias": ["Owen"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "63"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did the exhaust port the Rebel pilots had to target lead directly to?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The reactor system",
            "alias": ["Reactor System", "Reactor"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "64"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'There'll be no escape for the princess this time'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "C-3PO",
            "alias": ["C3PO", "C3P0", "C-3P0"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "65"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many TIE fighters make up a typical attack squadron?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Twelve",
            "alias": ["12"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "66"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many laser cannons does the TIE Advanced x1 have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Two",
            "alias": ["2"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "67"
        },
        {
            "question": "On what level was Princess Leia being held prisoner?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Level five",
            "alias": ["5", "Five", "Level 5"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "68"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Luke bulls-eye womp rats?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Beggar's Canyon",
            "alias": ["Beggars Canyon", "At Beggar's Canyon", "At Beggars Canyon", "In Beggar's Canyon", "In Beggars Canyon"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "69"
        },
        {
            "question": "What cellblock was Chewbacca supposedly being transferred to while rescuing Princess Leia?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Cellblock 1138",
            "alias": ["1138", "block 1138"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "70"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did C-3PO 'thank the Maker' for?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "An oil bath",
            "alias": ["Oil bath", "bath"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "71"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Admiral came out of lightspeed too close to the Hoth System?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Admiral Ozzel",
            "alias": ["Ozzel"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "72"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was wrong with R5-D4?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "It had a bad motivator",
            "alias": ["bad motivator", "He had a bad motivator", "had a bad motivator", "a bad motivator", "Motivator blew"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "73"
        },
        {
            "question": "On the first Death Star, which trash compactor were Luke, Han, Leia, and Chewbacca trapped in?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "32-5-3827",
            "alias": ["3253827", "32 5 3827"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "74"
        },
        {
            "question": "What were Han Solo's last words to Luke before the Battle of Yavin?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "May the Force Be With You",
            "alias": ["May the Force Be With u"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "75"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'I find your lack of faith disturbing'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Darth Vader",
            "alias": ["Vader"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "76"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'You were right about one thing, Master.  The negotiations were short'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "77"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who owned Anakin before Watto?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Gardulla the Hutt",
            "alias": ["Gardulla", "His Mother"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "78"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Rodian accompanied Jabba to confront Han Solo in Mos Eisley?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Thuku",
            "alias": ["Not Greedo"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "79"
        },
        {
            "question": "What aspect of the Force was most important to Qui-Gon?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The living Force",
            "alias": ["living Force", "The living", "living"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "80"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Queen Amidala's birth name?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Padmé Naberrie",
            "alias": ["Padme Naberrie", "Naberrie"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "81"
        },
        {
            "question": "On which planet did Obi-Wan and Qui-Gon first form a connection?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bandomeer",
            "alias": ["Bandomere"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "82"
        },
        {
            "question": "What species is also know as a 'snow lizard'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Tauntaun",
            "alias": ["Taun-Taun", "A tauntaun", "A taun-taun", "A taun taun", "taun taun"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "83"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'They can't have disappeared.  No ship that small has a cloaking device'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Needa",
            "alias": ["Needa"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "84"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which rebel pilot reported they had found Han and Luke on Hoth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Rogue Two",
            "alias": ["Rogue 2"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "85"
        },
        {
            "question": "To whom did Darth Vader make a point of stressing, 'No disintegrations'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Boba Fett",
            "alias": ["Boba"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "86"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did not concern Darth Vader, while talking to Admiral Piett?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Asteroids",
            "alias": ["The Asteroids", "Asteroid Field", "The Asteroid Field"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "87"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was in zone twelve, moving East?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The probe droid",
            "alias": ["Probe Droid"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "88"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which actor was inside R2-D2?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Kenny Baker",
            "alias": ["K Baker"],
            "category": "sw",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "89"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Good against remotes is one thing.  Good against the living, that's something else.'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Han Solo",
            "alias": ["Han", "Solo"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "90"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which species' culture is based solely on hunting and tracking those weaker than themselves?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Trandoshans",
            "alias": ["The Trandoshans", "Trandoshan"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "91"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Imperial Officer was in charge of the ground assault against the Rebels on Hoth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General Veers",
            "alias": ["Veers"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "92"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first tail gunner to harpoon an AT-AT during the Battle of Hoth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Wes Janson",
            "alias": ["Wes"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "93"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was in charge of Echo Base?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General Rieekan",
            "alias": ["Rieekan"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "94"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Han Solo's rank during the Battle of Hoth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain",
            "alias": ["Captain Han Solo", "Captain Solo"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "95"
        },
        {
            "question": "Luke, Han, Leia, and Chewbacca couldn't blast their way out of the trash compactor because it was _____ sealed", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "magnetically",
            "alias": ["magneticaly"],
            "category": "anh",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "96"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Luke's rank during the Battle of Hoth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Commander",
            "alias": ["Commander Skywalker", "Commander Luke Skywalker"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "97"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'I am not a committee!'", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Princess Leia",
            "alias": ["Leia", "Leia Organa", "Princess Leia Organa"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "98"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Echo Three?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Luke Skywalker",
            "alias": ["Luke"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "99"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'You truly belong with us here among the clouds'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Lando Calrissian",
            "alias": ["Lando"],
            "category": "esb",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "100"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who established a new Droid factory on Metalorn at the request of Count Dooku?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Wat Tambor",
            "alias": ["Tambor"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "101"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Vurk was seated in Chancellor Palpatine's box at the Galaxies Opera House?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sweitt Concorkill",
            "alias": ["Concorkill", "Sweitt"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "102"
        },

        {
            "question": "What Wookiee is the leader of the city Kachirho on Kashyyyk?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Tarfful",
            "alias": ["Tarful", "Tarfull"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "103"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Senator Mon Mothma's home planet?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Chandrila",
            "alias": ["Chandrila"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "104"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who, according to Obi-Wan Kenobi, had to be the poster boy?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
            "alias": ["Anakin", "Ani"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "105"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is Rystall Sant from?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "New Bornelax",
            "alias": ["Bornelax"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "106"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the Mon Calamari representative from Mon Calamari?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Meena Tills",
            "alias": ["Meena", "Tills"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "107"
        },
        {
            "question": "What clone trooper shot down Plo Koon during Order 66?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Jag",
            "alias": ["Jag", "Clone Trooper Jag"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "108"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the administress to the Commerce Guild Presidente?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Cat Miin",
            "alias": ["Cat", "Miin"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "109"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Wookiee was considered a master of the ryyk blade?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Salporin",
            "alias": ["Salporin"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "110"
        },
        {
            "question": "What politician split his time between estates on Coruscant, Ghorman and Sern Prime?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Fang Zar",
            "alias": ["Fang", "Zar"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "111"
        },
        {
            "question": "On Polis Massa, who told Yoda that Obi-Wan Kenobi had made contact?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["Bail", "Organa"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "112"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sheltay Retrac worked for which senator?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["Bail", "Organa"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "113"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who retrieved Yoda after his battle with Emperor Palpatine?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["Bail", "Organa"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "114"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Mace Windu's homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Haruun Kal",
            "alias": ["Haruun", "Kal"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "115"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who suggested that Master Kenobi should lead the mission to Utapau?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ki-Adi-Mundi",
            "alias": ["KiAdiMundi", "Ki-Adi", "Ki Adi Mundi", "Ki Adi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "116"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Separatist leader was initially interested in General Grievous due to his particular gruesome war record?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "San Hill",
            "alias": ["San", "Hill"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "117"
        },
        {
            "question": "What bounty hunter did Count Dooku pair with Asajj Ventress in his fight against the Republic?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Durge",
            "alias": ["Durge"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "118"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of model ship was Luke playing with in his uncle's garage?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "A T-16 Skyhopper",
            "alias": ["T-16 Skyhopper", "T-16", "T16", "Skyhopper", "Sky hopper"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "119"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many daughters did Ki-Adi-Mundi have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Seven",
            "alias": ["7"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "120"
        },
        {
            "question": "Against what species were General Grievous and the Kaleesh in a battle before he joined the Separatists?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Huks",
            "alias": ["Hukks", "The Huks", "The Hukks"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "121"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which form of Lightsaber combat was Mace Windu a master?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Vaapad",
            "alias": ["Varpad"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "122"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many arms did General Grievous have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Four",
            "alias": ["4"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "123"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Mace Windu say surrounded the Chancellor?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The dark side of the force",
            "alias": ["dark side of the force", "dark side", "the dark side"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "124"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did it turn out was responsible for erasing all information about Kamino from the Jedi Temple Archives?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Count Dooku",
            "alias": ["Dooku"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "125"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Obi-Wan Kenobi's favoured style of Lightsaber combat?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Soresu",
            "alias": ["Soresu", "Form 3"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "126"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Obi-Wan Kenobi's rank in the Grand Army of the Republic?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General",
            "alias": ["General Kenobi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "127"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Padmé want to have her baby?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Naboo",
            "alias": ["On Naboo"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "128"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Ki-Adi-Mundi's rank during the Clone Wars?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General",
            "alias": ["General Ki-Adi-Mundi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "129"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who narrowly escaped an assassination attempt by Boba Fett on Xagobah?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Wat Tambor",
            "alias": ["Tambor"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "130"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old was Mace Windu when he joined the Jedi Council?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Twenty-eight",
            "alias": ["28"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "131"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Sith artifact did Darth Tyranus unleash on the Republic during the Clone Wars?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The Dark Reaper",
            "alias": ["Dark Reaper", "Reaper"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "132"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who retrieved Obi-Wan Kenobi's Lightsaber on Utapau?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Commander Cody",
            "alias": ["Cody"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "133"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which jedi helped fight the Quarren Isolationist League on Mon Calamari?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Kit Fisto",
            "alias": ["Fisto", "Master Fisto", "Master Kit Fisto"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "134"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who financed the rehabilitation of General Grievous?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "San Hill",
            "alias": ["Hill"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "135"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Delva Racine's occupation?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Fashion Designer",
            "alias": ["Fashion", "Designer"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "136"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who shouted, 'Then he's not dead!' when the shock troopers said they couldn't find Yoda?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mas Amedda",
            "alias": ["Amedda"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "137"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to legend, who could use the dark side of the Force to create life?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Darth Plagueis",
            "alias": ["Plagueis"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "138"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who, along with Tarfful, escorted Yoda to an escape pod after the battle on Kashyyyk?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Chewbacca",
            "alias": ["Chewie"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "139"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who replaced Senator Lexi Dio after she was assassinated?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Male-Dee",
            "alias": ["MaleDee", "Male Dee", "Dee"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "140"
        },
        {
            "question": "Following his duel with Master Yoda, what clone Captain did Emperor Palpatine ask to prepare his shuttle?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Kagi",
            "alias": ["Kagi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "141"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long had Chancellor Palpatine been in office when he was kidnapped?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Thirteen years",
            "alias": ["13 years", "13 year", "13 yrs", "13y"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "142"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who led the Battle of Kashyyyk?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Yoda",
            "alias": ["Master Yoda"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "143"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who discovered a secret Techno Union laboratory on Nelvaan?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
            "alias": ["Anakin"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "144"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'What an incredible smell you've discovered!' to Anakin?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "145"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one was Padmé's handmaidens? Ruwee, Motee, Yauee", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Motee",
            "alias": ["b"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "146"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Yoda tell Obi-Wan he had for him on Tatooine?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Training",
            "alias": ["More training"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "147"
        },
        {
            "question": "What name did Darth Sidious give his new apprentice?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Darth Vader",
            "alias": ["Vader"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "148"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who had good relations with the Wookiees?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Yoda",
            "alias": ["Master Yoda"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "149"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Jedi Master was riding a BARC speeder on Saleucami when Order 66 was given?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Stass Allie",
            "alias": ["Stass", "Allie", "Stas Allie"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "150"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which pilot exclaimed, 'Flying is for Droids!'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "151"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who helped Yoda defeat the Separatists and rescue Luminara Unduli and Barriss Offee on Ilum?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Padmé Amidala",
            "alias": ["Padme Amidala", "Padmé", "Padme", "Senator Amidala", "Senator Padme Amidala", "Senator Padmé Amidala"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "152"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was captured by Asajj Ventress and placed in a Sith torture mask that hindered his ability to use the Force?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "153"
        },
        {
            "question": "Into whose care did Bail Organa place R2-D2 and C-3PO?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Raymus Antilles",
            "alias": ["Antilles", "Raymus"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "154"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Darth Sidious' Sith Master?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Darth Plagueis",
            "alias": ["Plagueis", "Darth Plagueis the Wise"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "155"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Jedi fell prey to Order 66 on Felucia?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Aayla Secura",
            "alias": ["Secura", "Master Aayla Secura"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "156"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who urged Padmé to allow him to accompany her to Mustafar?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Typho",
            "alias": ["Typho"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "157"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the Ithorian Jedi assigned to protect Chancellor Palpatine on Coruscant?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Roron Corobb",
            "alias": ["Corobb", "Roron"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "158"
        },
        {
            "question": "What senator wore a molf-tasseled overcloak?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Chi Eekway",
            "alias": ["Eekway", "Chi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "159"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who killed Count Dooku?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
            "alias": ["Anakin", "Ani"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "160"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Jedi Master was taken prisoner on Brentaal IV?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Agen Kolar",
            "alias": ["Agen", "Kolar"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "161"
        },
        {
            "question": "What stranded Jedi trained Asajj Ventress when she was a child?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ky Narec",
            "alias": ["Ky", "Narec"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "162"
        },
        {
            "question": "From what animal's skull was General Grievous' facemask carved?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Huk",
            "alias": ["A Huk", "Hukk", "A Hukk"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "163"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who made contact with General Kenobi after he escaped Utapau?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["Bail", "Organa"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "164"
        },
        {
            "question": "When Obi-Wan was complaining, who said 'No loose wire jokes' to him?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
            "alias": ["Anakin", "Ani"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "165"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said 'Well, did you notice the shields are still up?' during the battle over Coruscant?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "166"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Chancellor Palpatine, Sith Lords are out specialty'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "167"
        },
        {
            "question": "What were Anakin's last words to Mace Windu?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "I need him!",
            "alias": ["I need him", "I need him.", "I need him!!", "I need him!!!"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "168"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Padmé give to Anakin in honour of his being given the rank of Jedi Knight?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "R2-D2",
            "alias": ["R2D2", "R2 D2", "R2", "Rtoo", "Artoo"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "169"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who lamented, 'So this is how liberty dies - to thunderous applause'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Padmé Amidala",
            "alias": ["Padme", "Padme Amidala", "Senator Amidala", "Padmé"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "170"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did General Grievous collect?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Lightsabers",
            "alias": ["Sabers", "Light swords", "Lightsaber", "Jedi Lightsabers", "Jedi Lightsaber"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "171"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who represented Kuat in the Senate?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Giddean Danu",
            "alias": ["Giddean", "Danu"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "172"
        },
        {
            "question": "After his actions on which planet was Anakin awarded the title of jedi Knight, foregoing the Trials?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Nelvaan",
            "alias": ["Planet Nelvaan", "On Nelvaan"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "173"
        },
        {
            "question": "To whom was Anakin Skywalker entrusted as a Padawan when Obi-Wan Kenobi was presumed killed in battle?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ki-Adi-Mundi",
            "alias": ["KiAdiMundi", "Ki-Adi", "Ki Adi Mundi", "Ki Adi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "174"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to legend, on what planet did Mace Windu retrieve the crystals to create his purple Lightsaber?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Hurikane",
            "alias": ["On Hurikane", "Planet Hurikane"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "175"
        },
        {
            "question": "With which Jedi Master did Bultar Swan lead forces on the planet Aargonar?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ki-Adi-Mundi",
            "alias": ["KiAdiMundi", "Ki-Adi", "Ki Adi Mundi", "Ki Adi"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "176"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Anakin follow to Yavin 4?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Asajj Ventress",
            "alias": ["Asajj", "Ventress"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "177"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was with Anakin in his vision of the cave on Dagobah?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn",
            "alias": ["Qui-Gon", "Qui Gon Jinn", "Qui Gon", "QuiGon", "Qui-Gon Jin"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "178"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which General in the Republic was assigned to protect Tipoca City when the Separatists attcked Kamino?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Shaak Ti",
            "alias": ["Shaak", "Jedi Shaak Ti"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "179"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the Utapaun Master of Port Administration?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Tion Medon",
            "alias": ["Medon", "Tion"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "180"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the consort of Duke Teta?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Koyi Mateil",
            "alias": ["Koyi", "Mateil"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "181"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Captain Davijaan's nickname?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Odd Ball",
            "alias": ["OddBall"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "182"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the Talz Jedi assigned to protect Chancellor Palpatine from Grievous on Coruscant?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Foul Moudama",
            "alias": ["Moudama", "Foul"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "183"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the battle above Coruscant, who was Squad Seven leader?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Davijaan (Odd Ball)",
            "alias": ["Captain Davijaan", "Odd Ball", "Oddball"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "184"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who adopted Padmé's daughter Leia?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["Bail", "Organa", "The Organas", "Senator Organa"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "185"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Tion Medon's aide?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Lampay Fay",
            "alias": ["Lampay", "Fay"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "186"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where was Count Dooku's hidden base in which he trained General Grievous?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The Trenchant Cruiser",
            "alias": ["Trenchant Cruiser", "The Trenchant"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "187"
        },
        {
            "question": "On which planet did Ki-Adi-Mundi die?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mygeeto",
            "alias": ["On Mygeeto"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "188"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who called Anakin, 'Jedi Scum'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General Grievous",
            "alias": ["Grievous"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "189"
        },
        {
            "question": "To whom did Count Dooku say, 'Don't let your pursuit of trinkets cloud your reality'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General Grievous",
            "alias": ["Grievous"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "190"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who trained General Grievous in the Lightsaber arts?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Count Dooku",
            "alias": ["Dooku"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "191"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said to Anakin, 'There is much fear that clouds your judgement'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mace Windu",
            "alias": ["Mace", "Windu", "Master Windu"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "192"
        },
        {
            "question": "On which planet did Obi-Wan and Anakin/Vader fight?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mustafar",
            "alias": ["On Mustafar"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "193"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many Jedi accompanied Mace Windu to arrest Chancellor Palpatine?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Three",
            "alias": ["3"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "194"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said to Obi-Wan, 'When have I ever let you down?'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Commander Cody",
            "alias": ["Cody"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "195"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour was Anakin's starfighter after he lost his red one?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Green",
            "alias": ["It was green", "Green and Grey", "Green and Gray", "Green + Grey", "Green + Gray"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "196"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many times does Obi-Wan say that Anakin has saved his life?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Nine",
            "alias": ["9"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "197"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Jedi is shown accompanying Yoda on Kashyyyk?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Luminara Unduli",
            "alias": ["Luminara", "Unduli"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "198"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many years after Attack of the Clones did Revenge of the Sith take place?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Three",
            "alias": ["3", "About three", "About 3"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "199"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who played Obi-Wan Kenobi?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ewan McGregor",
            "alias": ["Jesus", "Ewan Macgregor"],
            "category": "rots",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "200"
        },
        {
            "question": "What creature did Jabba flick off the balcony of his private box at the Boonta Eve Classic Podrace?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "A Dwarf Nuna",
            "alias": ["A Nuna", "Dwarf Nuna", "Nuna"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "201"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Hela Brandes' position on the Royal Advisory Council of Naboo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Music Advisor",
            "alias": ["Musician", "Music", "Musician Advisor", "Musical Advisor"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "202"
        },
        {
            "question": "To what rank did Boss Nass promote Jar Jar for bringing the Naboo and the Gungans together?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "General",
            "alias": ["A general", "General Jar Jar"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "203"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Senator was chosen to replace Valorum as Chancellor of the Republic?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Senator Palpatine",
            "alias": ["Palpatine", "Palps"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "204"
        },
        {
            "question": "What creature first attacked Obi-Wan, Qui-Gon and Jar Jar as they traveled through Naboo's core?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Opee sea killer",
            "alias": ["Opee", "Opee killer"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "205"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Mas Amedda's role in the Senate?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Vice Chair",
            "alias": ["Vice Chair"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "206"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour on Watto's dice meant Anakin would go free?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Blue",
            "alias": ["Dark blue", "light blue"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "207"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to Obi-Wan, how high was Anakin's midi-chlorian count?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Off the chart",
            "alias": ["Off the charts", "Higher than yoda's", "Higher than yodas", "More than yodas", "More than yoda's"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "208"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Qui-Gon Jinn's Padawan before he chose Obi-Wan Kenobi?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Xanatos",
            "alias": ["Xanatos"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "209"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many wives did Ki-Adi-Mundi have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Two",
            "alias": ["2"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "210"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many legs to destroyer Droids have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Two",
            "alias": ["2"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "211"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many eyes do Gran have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Three",
            "alias": ["3"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "212"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the traditional Tusken Raider weapon of choice?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Gaffi Stick",
            "alias": ["Gaffi", "A Gaffi Stick", "A Gaffi"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "213"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Dis sun doen murder to mesa skin'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jar Jar Binks",
            "alias": ["Jar Jar", "Binks", "Jarjar"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "214"
        },
        {
            "question": "How much did the gorg that Har Har was trying to eat in Mos Espa cost?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Seven Wupiupi",
            "alias": ["7 Wupiupi", "7", "Seven"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "215"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour was Diva Funquita's hair?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Red",
            "alias": ["Dark Red", "Light Red", "Redish"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "216"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who presided over the Bonta Eve Classic Podrace?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jabba the Hutt",
            "alias": ["Jabba"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "217"
        },
        {
            "question": "What aws Dud Bolt's homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Vulpter",
            "alias": ["Vulptar"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "218"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of Queen Amidala's handmaidens was chosen to act as her decoy? (TPM)", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sabé",
            "alias": ["Sabe"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "219"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Jedi Master trained Jedi Council member Saesee Tiin?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Master Omo Bouri",
            "alias": ["Omo Bouri", "Bouri", "Omo"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "220"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour was Obi-Wan's Lightsaber blade?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Blue",
            "alias": ["Light Blue"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "221"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Qui-Gon Jinn run into in the swamps of Naboo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jar Jar Binks",
            "alias": ["Jar Jar", "Binks"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "222"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Ki-Adi-Mundi think Anakin's thoughts dwelled on?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "His mother",
            "alias": ["Mother", "Anakin's mother", "Anakins mother", "His mum", "His mom"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "223"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many laser cannons did the Queen's Royal Starship have?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "None",
            "alias": ["0", "zero"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "224"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour was Diva Shaliqua's hair?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Blue",
            "alias": ["Dark blue", "Light Blue"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "225"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Jedi-in-hiding did Aurra Sing hunt down and murder on Tatooine?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sharad Hett",
            "alias": ["Sharad", "Hett"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "226"
        },
        {
            "question": "From which planet did Senator Aks Moe come from?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Malastare",
            "alias": ["From Malastare"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "227"
        },
        {
            "question": "What do gorgmongers sell?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Gorgs",
            "alias": ["Gorg"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "228"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old was Darth Maul when Darth Sidious discovered him?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Four",
            "alias": ["4"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "229"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the reigning champion of the Boonta Eve Classic Podrace until Anakin won?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sebubla",
            "alias": ["Sebulba"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "230"
        },
        {
            "question": "What, according to Yoda, was the path to the dark side?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Fear",
            "alias": ["Fear"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "231"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old was Queen Amidala when she was elected Princess of Theed?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Twelve",
            "alias": ["12"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "232"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to Anakin, Angels lived on the moons of which planet?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Iego",
            "alias": ["The moons of Iego"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "233"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Master Yoda tell Obi-Wan that he should be mindful", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "The future",
            "alias": ["future", "his future"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "234"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ruler of Naboo did Queen Amidala replace?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "King Veruna",
            "alias": ["Veruna"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "235"
        },
        {
            "question": "On what planet did Obi-Wan retrieve the crystals to build his Lightsaber?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ilum",
            "alias": ["On Ilum"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "236"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour was Qui-Gon's Lightsaber blade?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Green",
            "alias": ["Dark Green", "Light green"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "237"
        },
        {
            "question": "Against whom did Senator Amidala run in the election to rule Naboo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sio Bibble",
            "alias": ["Bibble"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "238"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Darth Maul use to locate Qui-Gon Jinn on Tatooine?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Probe Droids",
            "alias": ["Probe Droid", "Probe", "A probe droid", "A probe"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "239"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Feel, don't think.  Trust your instincts'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn",
            "alias": ["Qui-Gon", "Qui Gon Jinn", "Qui Gon", "QuiGon", "Qui-Gon Jin"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "240"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of the Gungan underwater city?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Otoh Gunga",
            "alias": ["Otoh"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "241"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what form are Neimoidians at birth?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Grubs",
            "alias": ["Grub"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "242"
        },
        {
            "question": "Roughly how many beings call Coruscant home?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "A trillion",
            "alias": ["trillion", "About a trillion"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "243"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who exclaimed, 'At last we will have revenge'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Darth Maul",
            "alias": ["Maul"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "244"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many fingers do Gungans have on each hand?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Four",
            "alias": ["4"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "245"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Chancellor Valorum's homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Coruscant",
            "alias": ["Coruscant"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "246"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Droid repaired the shield generator on Queen Amidala's Royal Starship?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "R2-D2",
            "alias": ["R2D2", "R2 D2", "R2", "Rtoo", "Artoo"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "247"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who told Queen Amidala that the death toll on Naboo was 'catastrophic'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Sio Bibble",
            "alias": ["Bibble"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "248"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'And you, young Skywalker, we shall watch your career with great interest'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Chanceller Palpatine",
            "alias": ["Palps", "Palpatine", "Sheev Palpatine", "Sheeve Palpatine", "Sheev", "Sheeve"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "249"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was often referred to as 'the quickest eyes on Naboo'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Panaka",
            "alias": ["Panaka"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "249"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour were Darth Maul's Lightsaber blades?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Red",
            "alias": ["Dark Red"],
            "category": "tpm",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "249"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who, according to Ki-Adi-Mundi, was 'a political idealist, not a murdered'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Count Dooku",
            "alias": ["Dooku"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "250"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Count Dooku's homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Serenno",
            "alias": ["Sereno"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "251"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Kaminoan Chief Scientist?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ko Sai",
            "alias": ["Kosai"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "252"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long did Cliegg Lars say Shmi Skywalker had been missing?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "A month",
            "alias": ["month", "a month or so"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "253"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Mas Amedda's homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Champala",
            "alias": ["Champala"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "254"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who introduced Obi-Wan Kenobi to Jango Fett?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Boba Fett",
            "alias": ["Boba"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "255"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Captain Panaka's nephew?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Typho",
            "alias": ["Typho"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "256"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Anakin's step-brother?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Owen Lars",
            "alias": ["Owen"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "257"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Project Coordinator for the clone army on Kamino?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Taun We",
            "alias": ["TaunWe"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "258"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Shmi Skywalker doing when she disappeared from the Lars homestead?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Picking Mushrooms",
            "alias": ["Mushroom picking", "Farming"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "259"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who exclaimed, 'Trule wonderful, the mind of a child is!'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Yoda",
            "alias": ["Master Yoda"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "260"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who thought that Jedi should be able to know the difference between knowledge and wisdom?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Dexter Jettster",
            "alias": ["Dexter", "Dexter Jetster"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "261"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was elected Queen of Naboo after Padmé Amidala's term ended?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Queen Jamillia",
            "alias": ["Jamillia", "Jamilia"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "262"
        },
        {
            "question": "When Anakin Skywalker was assigned to protect Senator Amidala, how long had it been since he's last seen her?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ten years",
            "alias": ["10 years", "10 yrs", "10yrs", "10years"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "263"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many terms did Amidala serve as Queen of Naboo before becoming Senator?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Two",
            "alias": ["2"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "264"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'I was recruited by a man called Tyranus on one of the moons of Bogden'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jango Fett",
            "alias": ["Jango"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "265"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Prime Minister of Kamino?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Lama Su",
            "alias": ["LamaSu"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "266"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who lost a leg in a skirmish with Tusken Raiders?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Cliegg Lars",
            "alias": ["Cliegg", "Clieg"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "267"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'Dellow Felegates' while addressing the Senate?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jar Jar Binks",
            "alias": ["JarJar", "Jar Jar", "Binks"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "268"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Jobal Naberrie's relationship to Padmé?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mother",
            "alias": ["Mum", "mom", "Her mother", "her mum", "her mom"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "269"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Jedi Luminara Unduli's Padawan?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Barriss Offee",
            "alias": ["Barriss", "Offee"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "270"
        },
        {
            "question": "What planet is Padmé on when she finally admits that she truly deeply loves Anakin?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Geonosis",
            "alias": ["On Geonosis"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "271"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Owen Lars' homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Ator",
            "alias": ["Ator"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "272"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to Sio Bibble, how many trials had Nute Gunray had before the Supreme Court for his involvement in the Battle of Naboo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Four",
            "alias": ["4"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "273"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who accompanied Anakin to Tatooine to look for his mother?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Senator Amidala",
            "alias": ["Padmé", "Padme", "Padme Amidala", "Padmé Amidala", "Senator Padmé Amidala"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "274"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Obi-Wan say Anakin could rival as a swordsman if he spent more time practicing?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Yoda",
            "alias": ["Master Yoda"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "275"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who replaced Captain Panaka as Senator Amidala's head of security?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Captain Typho",
            "alias": ["Typho"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "276"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who exclaimed, 'Around the survivors, a perimeter create!' on Geonosis?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Yoda",
            "alias": ["Master Yoda"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "277"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who claimed that Geonosians didn't trust bounty hunters?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Count Dooku",
            "alias": ["Dooku"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "278"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who would never join Count Dooku, according to Obi-Wan?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn",
            "alias": ["Qui-Gon", "Qui Gon Jinn", "Qui Gon", "QuiGon", "Qui-Gon Jin"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "279"
        },
        {
            "question": "What planet was Anakin Skywalker on when Obi-Wan Kenobi tried to contact him from Geonosis", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Tatooine",
            "alias": ["On Tatooine"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "280"
        },
        {
            "question": "What planet did Jango Fett live on? (AOTC)", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Kamino",
            "alias": ["On Kamino"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "281"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whose voice did Yoda hear when Anakin attacked the Tusken Raiders on Tatooine?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn's",
            "alias": ["Qui-Gon", "Qui Gon Jinn", "Qui Gon", "QuiGon", "Qui-Gon Jin", "Qui-Gons", "Qui Gon Jinns", "Qui Gons", "QuiGons", "Qui-Gon Jins", "Qui-Gon's", "Qui Gon Jinn's", "Qui Gon's", "QuiGon's", "Qui-Gon Jin's"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "282"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who askd Anakin, 'Maybe you could help with some deadbeats who owe me a lot of money?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Watto",
            "alias": ["Watto"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "283"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who replaced Jedi Master Yaddle on the Jedi Council? (AOTC)", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Shaak Ti",
            "alias": ["Shaak"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "284"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'For a mechanic, you do an excessive amount of thinking'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "C-3PO",
            "alias": ["C3PO", "C 3PO", "C3P0", "3PO"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "285"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which form of lightsaber combat did Obi-Wan specialise in?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Form III",
            "alias": ["Form 3", "3", "Three", "Soresu"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "286"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who slays the Acklay in the Geonosian arena?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
            "alias": ["Obiwan", "Kenobi", "Obi-Wan", "Obiwan Kenobi", "Obi", "Obi Wan"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "287"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'No friends, no enemies.  Only allies and adversaries'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jango Fett",
            "alias": ["Jango"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "288"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Ki-Adi-Mundi's homeworld?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Cerea",
            "alias": ["Cerea"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "289"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who killed the Reek in the Geonosian arena?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Jango Fett",
            "alias": ["Jango"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "290"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of armour did Jango Fett wear?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Mandalorian",
            "alias": ["Mandalorian armour", "Stolen Mandalorian Armour"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "291"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said, 'There hasn't been a full-scale war since the formation of the Republic'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Senator Bail Organa",
            "alias": ["Bail", "Bail Organa"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "292"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Anakin and Padmé disguise themselves as when they left Coruscant to go into hiding on Naboo?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Refugees",
            "alias": ["Refugees"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "293"
        },
        {
            "question": "What prominant feature do male Kaminoans have that female Kaminoans lack?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "A head fin",
            "alias": ["A fin", "A finn", "A head finn", "head fin", "head finn"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "294"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did Elan Sleazebaggano try to sell Obi-Wan Kenobi in the Outlander nightclub?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Death Sticks",
            "alias": ["Death sticks"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "295"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who pompously exclaimed, 'If an item does not appear in our records, it does not exist'?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Madame Jocasta Nu",
            "alias": ["Jocasta Nu", "Jocasta"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "296"
        },
        {
            "question": "What colour is the speeder Anakin chooses for the Coruscant chase?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "alias": ["Bright yellow"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "297"
        },
        {
            "question": "What creature injured Padmé in the Geonosian arena?", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Nexu",
            "alias": ["A Nexu"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "298"
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank: 'It has been far too long, ____ Kenobi'", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "Master",
            "alias": ["master"],
            "category": "aotc",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": "299"
        }
    ],
    "newquestions": [
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "", 
            "type": "Short", 
            "answer": "",
            "alias": [""],
            "category": "",
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "id": ""
        }
    ]
}
